https://www.bmwmotorcycle.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used by Pixel Motion (also referred to as “us”, “our” and “we”), the entity that operates this website and collects and controls the data transmitted to the website.  PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your PII.  Our privacy policy also covers how you can exercise your rights to request data that we have collected about you, to ask us to delete your information, and how we secure your information.
What information do we collect?
When using the website, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.  We collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with an individual consumer, household, or device
We have collected the following categories of personal information from consumers within the last twelve (12) months:
Category
Examples
A. Personal Identifiers.
A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, Social Security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers.
B. Geolocation data.
Physical location or movements.
C. Professional or employment-related information.
Current or past job history or performance evaluations.
D. Non-public education information
Education records directly related to a student maintained by an educational institution or party acting on its behalf, such as grades, transcripts, class lists, student schedules, student identification codes, student financial information, or student disciplinary records.
We may gather certain non-personally identifiable information regarding the means you use to access our site. This information may include the type and version of your browser, your service provider, your IP address, any search engine you may have used to locate the site, and navigational information about where you go on our website. We use this information to better serve you, help diagnose problems with our server, administer the Web site, and compile broad statistical data. If we associate non-personally identifiable information with personally identifiable information, we will consider that combination of data as PII and treat it in the ways described within this privacy policy.
When do we collect information?
We collect PII from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our site, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, or respond to a survey or marketing communication.  As discussed, below, we also use cookies that collect information when you surf our website.
How do we use information we collect?
We may use the information we collect from you to:
Improve our website in order to better serve you.
Allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
Administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
Do we disclose information?
Yes, sometimes.  In this section we explain when and to whom we disclose information.  We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer PII other than as described below.   You can opt-out of a sale by submitting a request here.  In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have disclosed the following categories of personal information for a business purpose:  Category A (Personal Identifiers).
Business Partners:
We host and operate this website on behalf of our business partner, the dealership whose contact information is listed in the “About Us” section of this website.  As part of this relationship, we may share PII with our business partner.  Information provided by you may be available to both us and our partners.  This privacy policy does not address how any third party, including our business partner, might treat your data.  You should review the privacy policies of our business partner to understand how they will handle your data.
Service Providers:
We may disclose your personal information to a third party for a business purpose.  When we disclose personal information for a business purpose, we enter a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to both keep that personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose except performing the contract.
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities, such as companies who provide customer support to you. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these business services.
Business Transfers:
In the event that we sell or transfer a particular portion of our business assets, our users’ information may be transferred as part of the transaction. If substantially all of our assets are acquired, user information may be transferred as part of the acquisition.
Compliance with Law/Safety:
We may disclose specific personal information based on a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to comply with or conform to the law or that such disclosure is necessary to protect the users of our website, the website itself, or the public.
With Your Affirmative Consent:
Other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will notify you when any of your PII might be shared with third parties and you will be given the prior opportunity to accept or decline to share that information.
Non-personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
How do we protect your information?
We take reasonable measures to secure your information. Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site.
We use regular Malware Scanning.  Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is accessible by a limited number of persons who are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.
Transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
Do we use ‘cookies’?
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
We use cookies to:
Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (such as, Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If you disable cookies, some features will be disabled.  As a result, some of our services will not function properly.
How does our site handle do not track signals?
We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.
Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?
We do not allow third party behavioral tracking.  As of the effective date of this Privacy Statement, there is no commonly accepted response for Do Not Track signals initiated by browsers, therefore we do not respond to them.
How you know what information we have about you or ask that we delete your information?
You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will disclose to you:
The categories of personal information we collected about you.
The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.
Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.
The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information.
The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you (also called a data portability request).
If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, two separate lists disclosing:
sales, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient purchased; and
disclosures for a business purpose, identifying the personal information categories that each category of recipient obtained.
You also have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected about you and retained, subject to certain legal exceptions.
Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will process your request, unless an exception applies.  And, if you requested that we delete your data, we will also direct our service providers to similarly delete your personal information from their records.  We will also pass your request along to our business partners.
To exercise these rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request in one of the ways listed below under “Contact Us.”  Only you, or someone you authorized to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child.  You may also submit your request online, here.
A verifiable consumer request must:
Provide enough information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative; and
Describe your request with enough detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.
We will not discriminate against you for submitting a request and we will not deny you goods or services, charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties, provide you a different level or quality of goods or services, or suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
How can you correct or update your information?
If your personal information changes, you may correct, update, or amend it by contacting us via one of the methods listed below under “Contact Us.”  We will respond to your request within 30 days.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Children’s Privacy:
This website is not directed to children under the age of thirteen, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen on the site. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the age of thirteen on the site, we will delete the information from our records.
Updates to Our Privacy Policy:
This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically to reflect changes in our online information practices.  If we make any material changes, we will notify you by a prominent notice on our site.  Please check back from time to time to be aware of any changes to the Privacy Policy.
Agreement to Privacy Policy:
Your use of this site constitutes acceptance of the provisions of this Privacy Policy and your continued usage after such changes are posted constitutes acceptance of each revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any revised policy, please exit the site immediately.
Contact Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
pixelmotion.com
19600 Fairchild Rd Suite 360
Irvine, CA 92612
Data Request / Do Not Sell My Information
855-354-0120
privacy@pixelmotion.com
Last Edited on December 31, 2019
All New InventoryUsed InventoryFinancingSchedule ServiceBMW Motorcycles of San Francisco790 Bryant Street, San Francisco, CA 94107Get DirectionsCall us today!Sales: 415-503-9954Service: 415-503-9955Parts: 415-503-9956SalesSales Department HoursMonday: ClosedTuesday: 9:00am - 6:00pmWednesday: 9:00am - 6:00pmThursday: 9:00am - 6:00pmFriday: 9:00am - 6:00pmSaturday: 9:00am - 5:00pmSunday: Closed
©2020. BMW Motorcycles of San Francisco. All Rights Reserved.
Directions
Privacy
Terms
Contact Us
Sitemap
Click to call sales
While great effort is made to ensure the accuracy of the information on this site, errors can occur.
Please verify all pricing information with a customer service representative.
This is easily done by calling us or visiting us at the dealership.
My Vehicles
Listed below are your saved and recently viewed vehicles
CLOSE X
My Saved Vehicles ()
My Recently Viewed Vehicles ()
Compare
Vehicles
|
Logout
You can also view your saved vehicles on other devices.
Sign up
Sign In
Save your vehicles.
Have your vehicles with you
Save your favorite vehicles for later viewing on your desktop or mobile devices.
Recently Viewed Vehicles
Keep track of all the vehicles you've viewed for a better car shopping experience.
Compare saved vehicles
Narrow your search by comparing your favorite vehicles.
Log in to view your saved vehicles.
Enter your email
Sign Up
Sign In
Already registered? Sign in.
Or sign up to access your saved vehicles and
recently viewed vehicles on all your devices.
Vehicle Comparison
CLOSE
Condition
Price
Year
Make
Model
Trim
Select total out of pocket
$0 out of pocket$1 to $500 out of pocket$501 to $1,000 out of pocket$1,001 to $1,500 out of pocket$1,501 to $2,000 out of pocket$2,001 to $2,500 out of pocket$2,501 to $3,000 out of pocketOver $3,001 out of pocket
Select Your Mileage
10,000 mi. / yr
12,000 mi. / yr
15,000 mi. / yr
First Name
Last Name
Phone
Message
Zip Code*Message
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Start My Purchase
×
Schedule Service
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeDate
Date Format: MM slash DD slash YYYY
Date entered above will be confirmed by a service advisor.What service do you need?
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Order Parts
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeWhat parts are you looking for?
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Value Your Trade
What vehicle are you interested in?
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeWhat vehicle are you trading in?Trade In Image 1Trade In Image 2Trade In Image 3Trade In Image 4Trade In Image 5Trade In Image 6Trade In Image 7
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Make an Offer
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeMessage
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Check Availability
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeMessage
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Special Offers
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip CodeMessage
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Commercial Request
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip Code
New (709)
Ram (262)
Model
Ram 1500
Ram 2500
Ram 3500
Ram ProMaster 2500
Ram ProMaster 3500
Ram ProMaster 1500
Ram ProMaster City
Year
2016
2017
Message
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
×
Contact Us
Name*
First
Last
Phone*Email*
Zip Code*Message
By submitting your contact information, you consent to be contacted by telephone about purchasing a vehicle or obtaining vehicle financing. Clicking on the Submit button above is your electronic signature.
Models
AdventureHeritageRoadsterSportTourUrban Mobility20212021 K 1600 Grand America2019C 400 X2019C 650 GT2020C 650 GT2018C Evolution2021F 750 GS2021F 750 GS2020F 750 GS2021F 850 GS2020F 850 GS2021F 850 GS2020F 850 GS Adventure2021F 850 GS Adventure2021 F 850 GS Adventure2020F 900 R2021F 900 R2020F 900 XR2021F 900 XR2020G 310 GS2019G 310 GS2019G 310 R2020G 310 R2019K 1600 B2020K 1600 B2021K 1600 B2020K 1600 Grand America2019K 1600 Grand America2019K 1600 GT2020K 1600 GT2019K 1600 GTL2021K 1600 GTL2020K 1600 GTL2021M 1000 RR2019R 1250 GS2021R 1250 GS2020R 1250 GS2021R 1250 GS2021R 1250 GS2020R 1250 GS Adventure2021R 1250 GS Adventure2020R 1250 R2021R 1250 RS2020R 1250 RS2020R 1250 RT2021R 182021R 18 Classic2020R nineT2019R nineT2020R nineT /52020R nineT Pure2020R nineT Scrambler2021S 1000 R2020S 1000 R2020S 1000 RR2020S 1000 XR2021S 1000 XR2021S1000 RR
